A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, South and Southeast Asia, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia Field Office Files FA648
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, II
  - Burma -- Administration, 1961 (Box 2)
  - Burma -- Documents, [1962] (Box 2)
  - Burma -- General, 1962-1969 (Box 2)
  - Burma -- Program -- Supervised Credit Project, 1959-1962 (Box 2)
  - Burma -- Program -- Project Data, Final Reports, etc. (1), 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Burma -- Program -- Project Data, Final Reports, etc. (2), 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Cambodia, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Ceylon, 1963-1964 (Box 3)
  - Colombo Plan, 1962-1964 (Box 3)
  - Colombo Plan -- Technical Assistance, 1964-1968 (Box 3)
  - Communications, 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Council for International Progress in Management -- Grant Actions, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Council for International Progress in Management -- General Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning and Administration (R. Vernon -- Consultant), 1962-1969 (Box 3)
  - Economic Commission for Asia and the Far East (ECAFE) -- General, 1962-1967 (Box 3)
  - Economist -- Statistician, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Educational Television -- General, 1962 (Box 3)
  - European Technical Assistance, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Fiscal Policy and Economic Planning -- General Correspondence [PHOTOS], 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Fiscal Policy and Economic Planning -- General Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 3)
  - Fiscal Policy and Economic Planning -- Grant Actions, 1960-1965 (Box 3)
  - Forestry, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Franklin Publications, 1964-1970 (Box 3)
  - Hong Kong, 1963-1964 (Box 3)
  - India, 1964-1969 (Box 3)
  - Industrial Economist, 1964 (Box 3)
  - International Press Institute, 1962 (Box 3)
  - International Conference on Southeast Asian Studies, Feb 23-26, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Japan, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Labor Relations, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Language Teaching, 1960-1966 (Box 3)
  - Law Development, 1962-1967 (Box 3)
  - Manpower Development, 1964-1966 (Box 3)
  - Malaya -- Agricultural Development Council, Inc., 1964-1968 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Agricultural Diversification -- Project Correspondence, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Agricultural Diversification -- Correspondence and Memoranda, Jan-Jun 1963 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Agricultural Diversification -- Efferson Diary, 1963 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Agricultural Diversification -- Correspondence and Memoranda, Jul 1963-1964 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Agricultural Diversification -- Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Agricultural Diversification, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Asian-American Assembly, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Bank Negara -- Training, 1963-1966 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Development Programming, 1961-1965 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Development Programming, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Education, 1963-1966 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Family Planning, Aug 1963-Aug 1964 (Box 4)
  - Malaya -- Family Planning, Jul-Dec 1965 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- Family Planning, Jan-Apr 1966 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- Family Planning, May-Dec 1966 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- Family Planning, Jan-May 1967 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- Family Planning, Jun-Dec 1967 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- Family Planning, Jan-May 1968 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- Family Planning, Jun-Dec 1968 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- Forest Technology, 1963-1966 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- General, 1962-1966 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- General, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- Labor Research and Training, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- Land Tenure, 1963-1965 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- Land Tenure, Jun 1965 (Box 5)
  - Malaya -- Land Tenure -- Documents, 1962-1964 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- Library Development, 1962-1964 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- Library Development -- Swank & Danton Report, Aug 1963 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- Library Development, 1963-1968 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- Management Training, 1962-1967 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- Management Training, 1963-1968 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- Manpower, Jun 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- Miscellaneous, 1962-1966 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- National Art School, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- Peace Corps, 1961-1967 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- Primate Research Center (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- Tropical Fish Culture Research Institute, 1964-1969 (Box 6)
  - Malaya -- University of Malaya -- General, 1961-1966 (Box 6)
  - Malaysia -- Mara Institute of Technology -- RIDA, 1966-1972 (Box 6)
  - Management Training and Education -- Malaysian Institite of Management -- Singapore Institute of Management -- Thai Management Association, 1970-1974 (Box 6)
  - New Guinea, 1961-1963 (Box 6)
  - Nutrition, 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Oceanography, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Overseas Development -- General, 1962-1964 (Box 6)
  - Overseas Development -- General, 1965-Mar 1966; Photos (Box 6)
  - Overseas Development -- General Correspondence, Apr-Dec 1966 (Box 7)
  - Overseas Development -- General, 1967 (Box 7)
  - Overseas Development -- General, Jan-Sep 1968 (Box 7)
  - Overseas Development -- General, Oct-Dec 1968 (Box 7)
  - Overseas Development -- General, Jan-Jul 1969 (Box 7)
  - Overseas Development -- General, Aug-Dec 1969 (Box 7)
  - Overseas Development, Jan-Jul 1970 (Box 7)
  - Overseas Development, Aug-Dec 1970 (Box 7)
  - Overseas Development, Jan-Jul 1971 (Box 7)
  - Overseas Development -- Mexico Conference - Background Papers, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Overseas Development -- South and Southeast Asia Program, 1961-Mar 1965 (Box 8)
  - Overseas Development -- Representatives Conference -- Logistics, Jan 1964 (Box 8)
  - Overseas Development -- Representatives Conference -- Kuala Lumpor, Jan 1964 (Box 8)
  - Oxford -- Southeast Asia Studies, 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Pacific Islands, 1962-1968 (Box 8)
  - Pakistan (Planning Commission), 1962-1965 (Box 8)
  - Philippines -- Miscellaneous, 1963-1968 (Box 8)
  - Population -- Family Planning, 1961-1964 (Box 8)
  - Population -- Family Planning, 1964-1965 (Box 8)
  - Population -- Family Planning, 1965-1966 (Box 8)
  - Population -- Family Planning, 1967-Jul 1969 (Box 8)
  - Population -- Family Planning -- General Correspondence, Jan-Apr 1971 (Box 8)
  - Population and Family Planning -- General Correspondence, May-Jun 1971 (Box 9)
  - Population and Family Planning -- General Correspondence, Jul-Aug 1971 (Box 9)
  - Population and Family Planning -- General Correspondence, Sep-Dec 1971 (Box 9)
  - Population and Family Planning -- General Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1972 (Box 9)
  - Population and Family Planning -- General Correspondence, Mar-Apr 1972 (Box 9)
  - Population and Family Planning -- General Correspondence, May-Jun 1972 (Box 9)
  - Population and Family Planning -- General Correspondence, Jul-Aug 1972 (Box 9)
  - Population and Family Planning -- General Correspondence, Sep-Dec 1972 (Box 9)
  - Population and Family Planning -- General Correspondence, Jan-Apr 1973 (Box 9)
  - Population and Family Planning -- General Correspondence, May-Dec 1973 (Box 9)
  - Population -- Policy Research, Dec 1970-Jul 1972 (Box 9)
  - Population -- Policy Research, Oct 1972-Jul 1975 (Box 10)
  - Population -- Survey Mission Report (1), 1963 (Box 10)
  - Population -- Survey Mission Report (2), 1963 (Box 10)
  - Population -- Survey Mission Report (Other Countries), [1963] (Box 10)
  - Population -- University of Chicago, 1963 (Box 10)
  - Public Management Review, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Regional -- General, 1962-1965 (Box 10)
  - Science Teaching, 1963-1964 (Box 10)
  - Singapore, 1961-1967 (Box 10)
  - Singapore -- General, 1969-1971 (Box 10)
  - Singapore -- Government Exemption Negotiation, Oct 1965-Dec 1968 (Box 10)
  - Singapore -- Government Exemptions, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Singapore -- Family Planning, 1963-Jun 1966 (Box 10)
  - Singapore -- Family Planning, Jul-Dec 1966 (Box 10)
  - Singapore -- National Library, 1963-1969 (Box 10)
  - Singapore -- University -- Department of Music, 1962-1963 (Box 10)
  - Singapore -- University -- Electronic Computer Center, 1962-1963 (Box 10)
  - Singapore -- University of Singapore -- Faculty of Social Science, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Singapore -- Urban Development, 1962-1967 (Box 10)
  - Taiwan, 1962-1963 (Box 10)
  - Technical Training, 1962-1967 (Box 10)
  - Thailand -- General, Jan 1967 (Box 10)
  - Urban Development, 1961-1962 (Box 10)
  - United Nations -- Food and Agriculture Organization, 1962-1963 (Box 10)
  - United Nations -- UNESCO, 1963-1967 (Box 10)
  - Vietnam, 1961-1965 (Box 10)
  - Western Samoa, 1962-1963 (Box 10)